Italian Painting Photograph Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- S (Box 177)
  - Individual Artists S., 1265 (Box 177)
    - Sellaio, Jacopo del, 1441-1493., 39 (Box 184)
    - Sesto, Cesare da, 1480-1521., 22 (Box 184)
    - Severini, Gino, 1883-1966., 24 (Box 184)
    - Signorelli, Luca, 1445/50-1553., 162 (Box 184)
      - Drawings., 15 (Box 184)
      - Paintings., 147 (Box 184)
        - Locations not noted and private collections., 4 (Box 184)
        - Miscellaneous cities., 58 (Box 184)
        - Florence., 10 (Box 184)
        - London., 16 (Box 184)
        - New York., 4 (Box 184)
        - Orvieto., 23 (Box 184)
        - Paris., 7 (Box 184)
        - Rome., 15 (Box 184)
        - Washington, D.C., 10 (Box 184)
    - Signorini, Telemaco, 1835-1901., 19 (Box 184)
    - Simone Martini, 1283-1344., 177 (Box 184)
      - Locations not noted., 3 (Box 184)
      - Miscellaneous cities., 23 (Box 184)
      - Antwerp., 15 (Box 184)
      - Assisi., 49 (Box 184)
      - Florence., 16 (Box 184)
      - Naples., 11 (Box 184)
      - Orvieto., 5 (Box 184)
      - Paris., 5 (Box 184)
      - Pisa., 11 (Box 184)
      - Rome., 5 (Box 184)
      - Siena., 34 (Box 184)
    - Sironi, Mario, 1885-1961., 9 (Box 185)
    - Sodoma, Il, 1477-1549., 102 (Box 185)
      Also known as Giovanni Antonio Bazzi.
      - Drawings., 6 (Box 185)
      - Paintings., 96 (Box 185)
        - Locations not noted., 3 (Box 185)
        - Miscellaneous cities., 21 (Box 185)
        - Rome., 7 (Box 185)
        - Siena., 65 (Box 185-, Box 186)
    - Sogliari, Giovanni Antonio, 1492-1544., 7 (Box 186)
    - Solario, Andrea, 1460-1520., 22 (Box 186)
    - Solimena, Francesco, 1657-1747., 27 (Box 186)
    - Spada, Lionello, 1576-1622., 6 (Box 186)
    - Spagna, Giovanni, c.1450-1528., 19 (Box 186)
    - Spinello, Aretino, c.1350-1411., 34 (Box 187)
    - Squarcione, Francesco, 1394-1474., 3 (Box 187)
    - Stanzione, Massimo, 1585-1656., 9 (Box 187)
    - Stefano, Paolo di, 1397-1479., 5 (Box 187)
    - Stefano da Verona, c.1374-after 1438., 12 (Box 187)
    - Strozzi, Bernardo, 1581-1644., 34 (Box 187)
      - Drawings., 4 (Box 187)
      - Paintings., 30 (Box 188)
- T (Box 188)
  - Miscellaneous Artists T., 42 (Box 188)
    - Talpino, Enea, c.1550-1626., 1 (Box 188)
    - Tamagni da San Gimignano, 1492-1530., 1 (Box 188)
    - Tanzio da Varallo, 1575-1635., 4 (Box 188)
    - Tassi, Agostino, c.1580-1644., 3 (Box 188)
    - Tavarone, Lazzaro, 1556-1641., 1 (Box 188)
    - Tempesta, Antonio, 1555-1630., 2 (Box 188)
      Works done with Giovanni Senese.
    - Tempesti, Giovanni Battista, 1730-1804., 1 (Box 188)
    - Testa, Pietro, 1611-1650., 4 (Box 188)
    - Tiarini, Allesandro, 1577-1668., 2 (Box 188)
    - Tibaldi, Pellegrino, 1527-1596., 4 (Box 188)
    - Tiberio d'Assisi, c.1470-1524., 2 (Box 188)
    - Tito, Ettore, 1859-1941., 1 (Box 188)
    - Tivoli, Serafino de, 1826-1892., 3 (Box 188)
    - Todeschini, 1710-1736., 1 (Box 188)
    - Toma, Gioacchino, 1831-1891., 2 (Box 188)
    - Tosi, Arturo, 1871-., 1 (Box 188)
    - Tosini, Michele, 1501-1577., 4 (Box 188)
    - Travi, Antonio, 1608-1665., 1 (Box 188)
    - Trevisani, Angelo, 1689-1746., 1 (Box 188)
    - Treviso, Girolamo da, c.1450-c.1496 (?)., 1 (Box 188)
    - Turchi, Alessandro, 1582-1648., 4 (Box 189)
  - Individual Artists T., 1263 (Box 189)
    - Taddeo di Bartolo, 1363-1422., 76 (Box 189)
      - Locations not noted., 5 (Box 189)
      - Miscellaneous cities., 20 (Box 189)
      - Montepulciano., 15 (Box 189)
      - San Gimignano., 13 (Box 189)
      - Siena., 23 (Box 189)
    - Tiepolo, Giovanni Battista, 1696-1770., 277 (Box 189)
      - Drawings., 85 (Box 189)
        - Miscellaneous cities and locations not noted., 52 (Box 189)
        - New Haven., 13 (Box 189)
        - New York., 13 (Box 189)
        - Williamstown., 7 (Box 189)
      - Paintings., 192 (Box 189)
        - Locations not noted., 15 (Box 190)
        - Miscellaneous cities., 82 (Box 190-, Box 191)
        - London., 14 (Box 191)
        - Milan., 6 (Box 191)
        - New York., 17 (Box 191)
        - Paris., 7 (Box 191)
        - Venice., 24 (Box 191)
        - Washington., 16 (Box 191)
        - Wurzburg., 10 (Box 191)
    - Tiepolo, Giovanni Domenico, 1727-1804., 101 (Box 191)
      - Drawings., 92 (Box 191)
        - Miscellaneous subjects., 34 (Box 192)
        - Punchinello Series., 58 (Box 192)
      - Paintings., 9 (Box 193)
    - Tintoretto, 1518-1594., 265 (Box 193)
      Also known as Jacopo Giacomo Robusti.
      - Drawings., 13 (Box 193)
      - Paintings., 252 (Box 193)
        - Locations not noted., 17 (Box 194)
        - Miscellaneous cities., 53 (Box 194-, Box 195)
        - Dresden., 8 (Box 195)
        - Hartford., 5 (Box 195)
        - London., 15 (Box 195)
        - Madrid., 7 (Box 195)
        - Milan., 10 (Box 195)
        - Munich., 6 (Box 195)
        - New York., 8 (Box 195)
        - Venice., 99 (Box 195)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 11 (Box 195)
          - Accademia., 21 (Box 195)
          - Ducal Palace., 16 (Box 195)
          - S. Maria dell'Orto., 9 (Box 196)
          - Scuola di S. Rocco., 42 (Box 196)
        - Vienna., 6 (Box 196)
        - Washington, D.C., 18 (Box 197)
    - Titian, 1477-1576., 422 (Box 197)
      - Drawings., 28 (Box 197)
      - Paintings., 394 (Box 197)
        - Locations not noted., 16 (Box 197)
        - Private collections., 11 (Box 198)
        - Miscellaneous cities., 56 (Box 198)
        - Berlin., 9 (Box 198)
        - Boston., 15 (Box 198)
        - Dresden., 11 (Box 199)
        - Edinburgh., 8 (Box 199)
        - Florence., 36 (Box 199)
        - London., 33 (Box 200)
        - Madrid., 33 (Box 200)
        - Munich., 8 (Box 200)
        - Naples., 9 (Box 200)
        - New York., 15 (Box 200)
        - Paris., 17 (Box 201)
        - Rome., 21 (Box 201)
          Includes a portfolio of prints of Sacred and Profane Love.
        - Venice., 45 (Box 202)
        - Vienna., 21 (Box 202)
        - Washington, D.C., 30 (Box 202)
    - Tito, Santi di, 1536-1603., 6 (Box 202)
    - Tommaso da Modena, 1325-1379., 5 (Box 202)
    - Torbido, Francesco, 1486-after 1562., 5 (Box 203)
    - Traini, Francesco, active 1321-1369., 43 (Box 203)
      - Miscellaneous subjects., 13 (Box 203)
      - Last Judgement., 12 (Box 203)
      - Triumph of Death., 18 (Box 203)
    - Traversi, Gaspare, 1732-1769., 11 (Box 203)
    - Trevisani, Francesco, 1656-1746., 10 (Box 204)
    - Tura, Cosimo, 1430-1495., 42 (Box 204)
- U (Box 204)
  - Miscellaneous Artists U., 8 (Box 204)
    - Giovanni da Udine, 1487-1564., 4 (Box 204)
    - Ugo da Carpi, c.1450-after 1525., 1 (Box 204)
    - Ussi, Stefano, 1822-1901., 3 (Box 205)
  - Individual Artists U., 189 (Box 205)
    - Paolo Uccello, 1397-1475., 174 (Box 205)
      - Drawings., 8 (Box 205)
      - Paintings., 166 (Box 205)
        - Miscellaneous cities and locations not noted., 26 (Box 205)
        - Florence., 73 (Box 205)
          - Cathedral/Duomo., 11 (Box 205)
          - S. Maria Novella., 29 (Box 205)
          - San Miniato., 9 (Box 205)
          - Uffizi, (The Rout of San Romano.), 24 (Box 205)
        - London., 37 (Box 205)
          - Miscellaneous subjects., 4 (Box 205)
          - Battle of San Romano., 33 (Box 205)
        - Paris., 12 (Box 205)
        - Urbino., 18 (Box 205)
    - Ugolino da Siena, -1399., 12 (Box 205)
    - Utili, Giovanni Battista, active 1475-1516., 3 (Box 205)
- V (Box 205)
  - Miscellaneous Artists V., 21 (Box 205)
    - Valenti, Italo, 1912-., 3 (Box 205)
    - Valeriani, Giuseppe, -1761., 1 (Box 205)
    - Vanni, Turino, active 1395., 1 (Box 205)
    - Varotari, Alessandro, 1588-1648., 2 (Box 205)
    - Vasta, Pietro Paolo, 1697-1760., 1 (Box 205)
    - Vedova, Emilio, 1919-., 2 (Box 205)
    - Venito, XV C., 1 (Box 205)
    - Venna, Lucio, 1897-., 1 (Box 205)
    - Vespignani, R., 1924-., 1 (Box 205)
    - Vicino da Ferrara, active c.1473., 1 (Box 205)
    - Vigoroso da Siena, XIII C., 3 (Box 205)
    - Vincenzo da Pavia, c.1500-1557., 1 (Box 205)
    - Vitale da Bologna, XIV C., 2 (Box 205)
    - Viterbo, Antonio, ?., 1 (Box 205)
  - Individual Artists V., 478 (Box 205)
    - Vaccaro, Andrea, 1604-1670., 5 (Box 205)
    - Vaga, Pierino del, 1501-1547., 20 (Box 205)
      - Drawings., 4 (Box 205)
      - Paintings., 16 (Box 205)
    - Vanni, Andrea di, 1332-1414., 19 (Box 206)
    - Vanni, Francesco, 1565-1609., 5 (Box 206)
    - Vanni, Lippo, active c.1341-1375., 6 (Box 207)
    - Vasari, Giorgio, 1511-1574., 34 (Box 207)
      - Drawings., 7 (Box 207)
      - Paintings., 27 (Box 207)
    - Vecchietta, Lorenzo, 1412-1480., 55 (Box 207-, Box 208)
    - Veronese, Paolo, 1528-1588., 220 (Box 208)
      - Drawings., 15 (Box 208)
      - Paintings., 205 (Box 208)
        - Locations not noted., 11 (Box 208)
        - Miscellaneous cities., 35 (Box 208)
        - Dresden., 14 (Box 208)
        - Florence., 12 (Box 208)
        - London., 13 (Box 208)
        - Madrid., 9 (Box 209)
        - Maser, Villa Barbaro., 17 (Box 209)
        - New York., 9 (Box 209)
        - Paris., 11 (Box 209)
        - Rome., 7 (Box 209)
        - Venice., 50 (Box 210)
        - Washington, D.C., 14 (Box 210)
        - School of Veronese., 3 (Box 210)
    - Verrocchio, Andrea del, 1435-1488., 53 (Box 210)
      - Drawings., 9 (Box 210)
      - Paintings., 44 (Box 211)
    - Viti, Tomoteo della, 1467-1523., 6 (Box 211)
    - Vivarini, Alvise, 1445-1505., 12 (Box 211)
    - Vivarini, Antonio, 1415-1476., 16 (Box 211)
    - Vivarini, Bartolomeo, 1432-1499., 27 (Box 212)
- Z (Box 212)
  - Miscellaneous Artists Z., 18 (Box 212)
    - Zais, Guiseppe, 1709-1784., 1 (Box 212)
    - Zanchi, Antonio, 1631-1722., 1 (Box 212)
    - Zanotti, Calisto Cavazzoni, 1825-1857., 2 (Box 212)
    - Zavattori, Gregorio, active 1453-1475., 1 (Box 212)
    - Zelotti, Giovanni Battista, 1526-1578., 2 (Box 212)
    - Zenale, Bernardo, 1436-1526., 3 (Box 212)
    - Zocchi, Guiseppe, 1711-1767., 2 (Box 212)
    - Zotto, Giovanni Francesco dal, c.1450-1510., 1 (Box 212)
    - Zucchi, Antonio, 1726-1795., 1 (Box 212)
    - Zucchi, Jacopo, 1541-1590., 4 (Box 212)
  - Individual Artists Z., 47 (Box 212)
    - Zandomeneghi, Federico, 1841-1917., 6 (Box 212)
    - Zoppo, Marco, 1433-1478., 7 (Box 212)
    - Zuccarelli, Francesco, 1702-1788., 18 (Box 212)
    - Zuccari, Federico, 1540-1609., 11 (Box 212)
    - Zuccari, Taddeo, 1529-1566., 5 (Box 213)